In this video, I will introduce the version generator function for you.
The new version has optimized the parameterized version function, also known as the version generator.
This function allows users to enter accurate measurement values or generate parameterized versions based on the reference image of the required version.
Therefore, users can quickly and accurately make the necessary versions based on actual data.
Let's take a closer look at its working principle.
When using the version generator to create a version, the system will automatically arrange and seal it according to the incoming virtual model.
Therefore, we need to load the virtual model first.
Enter the image of a virtual model woman.
Then double-click on the virtual model to load it in.
Next, please go to the main menu 2D version generator.
Under default, the clothing category is set to T-shirt.
Currently, the version generator only supports creating T-shirts.
The plan is in the future.
We will develop more categories, such as pants and skirts.
Here you can choose the T-shirt sleeve type.
Currently, the following types can be selected.
Decoration, insert sleeve or drop sleeve.
Let's choose the decoration type first.
Then you will see a list of measurements required for a created version.
There is a pull-down menu on the top, in which the standard is selected.
A transparent frame version will appear in the window of the 2D version window on the right.
The frame is automatically loaded with default measurement data.
In the version generator, you can freely configure which measurements to enter to create a version.
The pull-down menu will display the data based on the version type selected in the upper layer.
Provides two preset options, simple and regular.
These presets are designed around the common measurement data of each type.
Regular preset includes more detailed measurement values.
It is suitable for when you have all the necessary dimensions.
So that you can enter more measurement values to create.
The version is better suited to your desired design.
Next, let's click on the pull-down menu and select the simple menu.
Simple preset provides a set of simplified measurement projects.
You only need a few basic values to create a version.
It is suitable for the first time to create a version.
Or if there is no detailed measurement data.
First, click on the one on the right side of the title.
Show all measurement charts.
Each of the measurement projects are grouped together.
This will show the complete list of measurements that can be used.
Including the default hidden measurement value.
You can click on the detailed information icon in the upper right corner.
To control which measurement projects are in the active state or stop state.
According to the way you activate or stop the measurement.
The way of generating versions will also change.
For active projects, users directly enter the value.
And create versions based on these values.
On the other hand, for stopped projects.
Calculate the appropriate value based on actual data.
There is no need to enter the value and automatically react in the version.
This means that even if you do not enter all the values.
You can still generate accurate versions with the least number of values.
For example, in the current simple option.
The back piece only activates the full length.
Click on the measurement value and adjust the value by moving the mouse wheel.
Then you can see that the 2D window will also display the length indicator line.
The front length value is applied according to the back length value.
Let's click again.
Set the detailed information icon and activate the full length of the front piece.
At this time, when you modify the front length.
The length of the back piece will remain unchanged.
You can also see that when you modify the full length of the front piece.
The relevant value of the back piece will also change according to the input value of the front piece.
This is also the case when modifying the width.
In addition, if you have modified the measurement project.
It is different from the simple and regular provided by default.
You can see the pull-down menu at the top.
The name has been changed to user self-determination.
The user self-determination mode is actually to support users.
By configuring the measurement project they want to create a version option.
Even if you run the software again.
In setting the detailed information, the final measurement project of selection and setting will remain unchanged.
So you can continue to use them in the future.
Next, let's use the T-model to create a round table.
First, let's choose a simple menu at the top.
If the board is activated, the eye icon in front will be blue.
And it will be transparent in the window of the 2D pattern window on the right.
When you cancel the single eye icon.
It will change to gray to hide all measurements of the board.
And the board will disappear from the 2D window.
Let's click the eye icon again to activate the front piece.
On the right side of the unit part of the board.
You will see the symmetry and the left and right symmetry options.
In the default situation, the left and right symmetry is in use.
Because it usually uses this setting to create the front and back pieces.
Therefore, the frame board in the 2D window.
It also shows the form of the left and right symmetry board.
If you choose the symmetry board, it will be displayed as two symmetrical boards.
If you cancel the selection of two options, only half of the board will be generated.
Now let's choose the left and right symmetry again.
First, let's enter the total length of the round table.
We enter the total length according to the total length of the back piece.
Select the height point measurement.
Then when you click the input frame of the measurement value.
On the transparent frame board in the 2D window.
The measurement position guide line corresponding to the display will be shown at the same time.
When entering the value, please click the input frame of the measurement item.
Enter 600.
If you want to reset.
You can click the reset button on the right side of the measurement item.
The reset button can not only be used to reset each measurement item.
It can also be used to reset the entire board such as the front piece, the back piece and the sleeve.
Then I will enter again.
The total length of the piece is 620.
The value related to the width needs to be entered in the corresponding board total width value.
And the total length value can be entered by pressing the total length option.
Let's enter the total total length value.
Let's enter the width 160 in order.
Width input 400.
We will first select the measurement standard as the sleeve to the sleeve.
And enter the total total length value instead of the front piece.
Click the total length icon on the right side.
Then in the 2D window.
There will be a guideline line with the front piece and the back piece of the chest wide.
You can identify the position of the total length value.
Enter 1000 as the chest.
Enter the total length of the bottom width as 960.
Then enter the measurement value of the sleeve board.
First, let's enter the sleeve length.
Enter 570 to change it to a long sleeve.
Enter the width of the sleeve mouth as 240.
In order to adjust the quality in this state.
Let's change the menu from the top simple to normal.
Then show the rest of the detailed measurement projects.
At the same time, it will maintain the value entered in the previous simple.
Here we will additionally adjust the neck and shoulder length.
To adjust the depth of the front and back neck and shoulder angle.
First, enter 60 as the front neck.
Then set the shoulder length to 37.8 mm.
Turn to the back piece and enter 25 as the back neck.
In order to make the shoulder length of the back piece the same as the size of the front piece.
Enter 42.8 mm.
Then the sleeve and sleeve board is completed.
Because we want to make the collar.
So we need the sleeve pattern and the lower pattern pattern.
The default settings of the front and lower and the lower pattern of the sleeve mouth are prohibited.
Let's activate it by pressing the eye icon in front of each part.
Then you can see that each pattern is activated and displayed in the 2D window.
Currently, the front and back of the sleeve can only be inserted at a height related length.
Click the upper right corner button.
Set the detailed information icon, roll down and select the upper and lower width in the upper and lower width from the sleeve opening and the lower and lower width.
Then click again to set the detailed information icon to exit the window.
Let's first enter the sleeve opening in order.
The upper width will be entered as 150.
Next, we will enter the lower and lower width before and after the input.
The lower and lower width of the two paper types are the same.
The seam line value is 60, and the slightly width value is 390.
By pressing the save button in the lower left corner, the value entered in this way can be saved as CSV file.
Then you can open the button on the right side of the single click to enter the previously saved CSV file,
and you do not need to manually enter the value again to easily modify the sheet in the generator.
Next, let's go through the instructions.
Click the Create button in the lower right corner to create a sheet.
In order to check whether the arrangement and sewing are automatically applied to the virtual model surroundings,
let's close the sheet generator window and check the 3D window.
You can see that the round collar is already arranged around the virtual model, and it has also been automatically sewn.
In order to prevent simulation conflicts, move the lower and lower white sheets slightly downwards and simulate.
Then we have created the round collar.
Next, let's based on the image of the AI creation sheet,
and create a sheet according to the image.
Let's delete the sheet you created and leave only the virtual model.
Click the AI generation sheet icon in the upper right corner of the sheet generator.
The AI generation sheet window will appear.
For the AI generation sheet, you can create a sheet through a prompt or a picture.
First, let's take a look at how to create a prompt.
First, select the type of version you want to create at the top.
Currently, the AI generation sheet can only create the version of T-shirt and other clothes.
In the future, we will develop various clothing types such as pants, skirts, etc.
Next, let's take a look at the text prompt window at the bottom.
In the text prompt window, you can enter the text prompt that describes the required version.
Click the key word suggestion on the first icon on the right.
You can choose to recommend key words for creating a version.
For example, clothes length, collar length, or sleeve length.
In the text prompt window, you can choose to recommend key words for creating a version.
Here, if you choose the desired key word,
you will see that these key words have been added to the text prompt window.
If you want to delete these key words again, you can click the X button.
Or, in the key word suggestion window, click the key word suggestion icon again.
To cancel the selection of key words,
click the start generation button.
The system will start generating the corresponding image according to the key word.
Even if there is a similar prompt,
the AI version generator will always create a new image.
However, at this time, if you activate this maintain prompt icon,
you can keep the existing results as much as possible,
add a prompt and update.
For example, you can keep the above options and click the maintain prompt icon.
Then, in the key word suggestion, click the U-shape.
After that, you can create the new image again.
Once again,
the new image is generated,
the prompt icon shows a major change.
There is a third code.
When you want to get inspiration, you can use it.
To change the prompt,
use the clear prompt word to close the prompt.
In the history window in the right-hand corner,
you can choose the name of the prompt.
Check the image list of the image created so far and the input prompt
And click the save button to save the desired result as an image file
Next, let's use the existing image file to create a sample
The category is still T-shape
Click the upload button to add the desired image
Then click on the bottom of the window to start creating
The generate button will convert it into a sample
Check the current sample window
You will find that the T-shape sample has been created according to the image
Click the close button to close the window
Then, according to the measurement value needed to modify the sample generated by AI
If you check the version of the generator window
You will find that the top category has been automatically identified and changed to T-shape
You can also see that it has been switched to the regular menu
And all relevant values ​​have been entered
In order to create the sample according to the most detailed measurement project
Now let's modify the sample
To create the T-shape and T-shape in the sample
First, change the T-shape to 600
At present, both the T-shape of the front and the T-shape of the back measurement project have been used
Therefore, they can be set separately
I now want the T-shape of the front to change according to the input of the back
Click on the Detailed Information icon to cancel the selection of the T-shape of the front
Then enter 600 as the T-shape of the back
As you can see
The front piece will be linked according to the total length of the back piece you input
The length will also be modified together
Then let's press the Create button to create the T-shape
In the T-shape of the T-shape
In order to measure the width and slope of the T-shape according to the HPS high and low points
The T-shape is shown separately as the front and back pieces along the gap of the T-shape
However, once the T-shape is created
The front and back T-shape will be merged according to the HPS
The corresponding gap will also be converted to the base line
Close the T-shape generator window
You can see that as long as the T-shape is automatically arranged and sealed according to the virtual model
Click on the Modify button and run the program
You can see the T-shape of the T-shape
It has become 3D clothing worn on the virtual model
The T-shape generator can not only be created according to the exact size of the T-shape
It can also be easily and accurately made in various styles through a single picture
So everyone can take advantage of this function when playing the board